Project Engineer Resume

Vladimir Timonin

Tel: +38(098)25-37-035

vtimonin1979@gmail.com E-mail:

Skype: vlad i mir

Year of birth: 1979 City: Kharkov

Objective

Project engineer position

Summary of Qualifications

11 years technical support and service in a telecommunication company 6 years development of telecommunication networks and security systems Knowledge/skills of designing in AutoCAD, Visio applications

Skills and knowledges

Applications: AutoCAD, Visio, MS Office

Engineering systems: control systems, security systems, telecommunication systems

Foreign language

English Intermediate

Professional Experience

12/2016 – present time

Position: Project Engineer at "Padio-Link" Company, Kharkov

Responsibilities:

- development of telecommunication networks and security systems;
- development of project documentation.

11/2016 - 12/2016

Position: Project Engineer at "Ukrnaftokhimproect" Company, Kharkov Responsibilities:

- development of telecommunication networks and security systems.

03/2015 - 06/2016

Position: Project Engineer at "IBC Solutions" Company, Moscow Responsibilities:

- development of building control systems;
- development of project documentation;
- corporate site support.

11/2012 - 01/2015

Position: Project Engineer at "Soyuzenergoproekt" Company, Kharkov Responsibilities:

- development of telecommunication networks and systems;
- development of project documentation.

07/2001 - 11/2012

Position: Engineer at "Ukrtelecom" Company, Kharkov Responsibilities:

- technical maintenance and service of telecommunication equipment;
- support and communications with customers.

Education

09/1996 - 06/2001

Kharkov National University of Radio Electronics. The specialist degree in Telecommunication Systems

Hobby

Sports, books, travels, photography